<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Random Walk</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="button_send">Send</string>
    <string name="intro_level1A">The pirate just arrived in a new harbour and is ready to go out, but he is aware that he might be tottering on his way back to the ship. \n \nTry helping him with choosing bar wisely to maximise his chances of arriving to the ship! \n \nChoose a starting point of the pirate\'s walk and observe his movement... \n \nBe prepared - even if you choose
    ideal starting point, due to waddling in pirate\'s walk you still might fall into the sea! \n \nTry walking couple of times.\nIf you are really unlucky, you will be able to change your starting point.</string>
    <string name="intro_level1B">\n\n\n\nThis time, pirate is not moving alone, he has your help! You will be able to help by tilting the phone and thus forcing his direction towards the boat. \n\n\n\nHowever, he\'s very strong and the movement has a great deal of randomness still. Try couple of times - until you arrive home and understand how the walk is modified by your help - the drift.</string>
    <string name="intro_level2A"></string>
    <string name="guite_level2a"></string>
    <string name="learn_more_main_menu">        The parrot\’s feather coloration
        pattern doesn\’t look like a
        perfect copy of its parents\’ one, with whom it shares the genetic heritage. Genetic
        differences occur due to a rearrangement of DNA during the reproduction (“crossover”) and
        unpredictable mutations.\n \n
        In general, patterns of pigmentation in multicoloured animals is not controlled only by their set of genes
        (“genotype”) but also the history and the environment contribute to their variability. \n
        Even if we could select the same genes, follow the same history, expose cells to the same
    environment, still organisms would display some difference in their observable features ("phenotype").
    \n \n Scientists have recently thought that randomness in the process of gene expression can be a
     major source of phenotype variability. It means that, if molecules of a specific type exist in few copies inside a cell,
     random effects stemming from their random walks can become important. \n \n What does it imply at the end of the day? Every
     individual in a population of living organisms is unique and differs from anyone else, even its twin or clone,
     in appearance and behaviour. \n \n Biologists refer to variation in measured levels of gene
    expression products(e.g. proteins) as "noise", regardless of the source. They call "extrinsic"
     the noise due to microscopic cell-to-cell differences of environment and history, "intrinsic" the
    one due to random fluctuations."</string>
    <string name="level2A_text">        You are about to enter one of the parrot\'s feather cell, where you will explore why each of these animals appear so colourful and diverse!\n\nNow instead following a pirate, follow the movements of big molecules - transcription factors inside the cell. As the transcription factors take part in the process called “gene expression” and play important role enabling the creation of mRNAs - try to create as much as possible of them!</string>

    <color name="Level1">#F1D495</color>
    <color name="Level1_game_background">#DED9D9</color>
    <color name="level2_game_background">#c2d5f0</color>
    <color name="Level2">#91C8C2</color>
    <color name="BlueLine">#5069a9</color>
    <color name="RedLine">#ef7861</color>
    <color name="GreenLine">#01a05f</color>
    <color name="YellowLine">#864ca3</color>

    <string name="title_activity_level1">Level1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2">Level2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_start">Random Walk</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2_animation">Level2Animation</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2_b">Level2BActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1a_game">Level1aGameActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1b_game">Level 1B</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2a_game">Level2</string>

</resources>
