<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Random Walk</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="button_send">Send</string>
    <string name="intro_level1A">The pirate just arrived in a new harbour and is ready to go out, but he is aware that he might be tottering on his way back to the ship. \n \nTry helping him with choosing bar wisely to maximise his chances of arriving to the ship! \n \nChoose a starting point of the pirate\'s walk and observe his movement... \n \nBe prepared - even if you choose
    ideal starting point, due to waddling in pirate\'s walk you still might fall into the sea! \n \nTry walking couple of times.\nIf you are really unlucky, you will be able to change your starting point.</string>
    <string name="intro_level1B">\n\n\n\nThis time, pirate is not moving alone, he has your help! You will be able to help by tilting the phone and thus forcing his direction towards the boat. \n\n\n\nHowever, he\'s very strong and the movement has a great deal of randomness still. Try couple of times - until you arrive home and understand how the walk is modified by your help - the drift.</string>
    <string name="intro_level2A"></string>
    <string name="guite_level2a"></string>
    <string name="learn_more_main_menu">
        Pirate’s walk:\n A mathematician would describe the pirate\'s movement as a “random walk” - because all the steps pirate takes have different lengths and seem to be in arbitrary direction. These processes, which include series of chance moves, are widespread in both daily life and scientific research: follow the link to see some examples: http://goo.gl/6ljFpC .
\n\nParrot\’s feather:\n Scientists have recently thought that randomness in the process of gene expression can be a major source of phenotype variability. It means that every individual in a population of living organisms is unique and differs from anyone else, even its twin or clone, in appearance and behaviour. Follow the link to learn about this phenomenon http://goo.gl/eLEFNc .
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_main_menu">
        The team:\nThe project “Random Walks” is created by Aleksandra Aloric, Silvia Bartolucci and Barbara Bravi, PhD students in the Disordered Systems group, King\'s College Mathematics department.\nThe app is developed by Sari Nusier, a Bachelor student of Computer Science and Management at King\'s College London.\nThe graphics is designed by Anne Odling Smee, Director of Design Science.\n\nFor more information visit our website at http://goo.gl/DFq44C.\n\nAcknowledgements:\nKing\’s College Cultural Institute Early Career Researchers (ECR) scheme and NETADIS (FP7 – Grant 290038).\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nDisordered Systems:\n http://www.kcl.ac.uk/nms/depts/mathematics/research/disorderedsys/index.aspx\n\nDesign Science:\nhttp://design-science.co.uk\n\nCultural Institute:\nhttp://www.kcl.ac.uk/cultural/culturalinstitute/index.aspx\n\nNETADIS:\nhttps://netadis.wordpress.com\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="level2A_text">        You are about to enter one of the parrot\'s feather cell, where you will explore why each of these animals appear so colourful and diverse!\n\nNow instead following a pirate, follow the movements of big molecules - transcription factors inside the cell. As the transcription factors take part in the process called “gene expression” and play important role enabling the creation of mRNAs - try to create as much as possible of them!</string>
    <string name= "level2a_endText">Transcription factors are constantly colliding with organelles and other smaller molecules
    which forces them to "random walk" and have variable chances to reach the promoter region. Also mRNAs are created with a certain probability (see learn more):
    their number will be responsible for the phenotype change.\n \n Did you manage this time to create some mRNAs? If you are
    not satisfied you can start the process again.. maybe the randomness characterising it will help you generate a different number of mRNAs. In the next level you will see the effect on the parrot feathers!</string>
    <color name="Level1">#F1D495</color>
    <color name="Level1_game_background">#DED9D9</color>
    <color name="level2_game_background">#c2d5f0</color>
    <color name="Level2">#91C8C2</color>
    <color name="BlueLine">#5069a9</color>
    <color name="RedLine">#ef7861</color>
    <color name="GreenLine">#01a05f</color>
    <color name="YellowLine">#864ca3</color>
    <color name="Bk0">#C1D5F0</color>
    <color name="Bk1">#CBD5EF</color>
    <color name="Bk2">#D5D5EF</color>
    <color name="Bk3">#E7D5EF</color>
    <color name="Bk4">#F3D5DF</color>
    <color name="Bk5">#FFD5DF</color>
    <color name="Bk6">#FFD9D6</color>
    <color name="Bk7">#FAD5CF</color>
    <color name="Bk8">#FAD6C8</color>
    <color name="Bk9">#D5D5EF</color>

    <string name="title_activity_level1">Level1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2">Level2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_start">Random Walk</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2_animation">Level2Animation</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2_b">Level2BActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1a_game">Level1aGameActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1b_game">Level 1B</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2a_game">Level2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2c_game">Level 2C</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1c_game">Level 1C</string>

</resources>
