<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Random Walk</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="button_send">Send</string>
    <string name="intro_level1A">The pirate has just arrived in a new harbour and is ready to go out, but he is aware that he might be tottering on his way back to the ship. \n \nTry helping him with choosing a position on the bar wisely, i.e. in such a way to maximise his chances of arriving to the ship! \n \nChoose a starting point of the pirate\'s walk and observe his movements… \n \nBe prepared - even if you choose
    an ideal starting point, due to the waddle of the pirate, he still might fall into the sea! \n \nTry a couple of times.\nIf you are really unlucky, you will be able to change your starting point.</string>
    <string name="end_level1A">\n \nThe type of walk we were observing in the pirate’s rambling is called \“Random walk\”: both the length and the direction of each step are unpredictable.\n\n
        We can\’t say much about the success of reaching the boat when we are looking at one trajectory, but when we are observing more trials of the pirate, we can claim that some choices of bars
are better than others… For example, what if you choose a starting point just opposite to the ship?</string>

    <string name="intro_level1B">\n\n\n\nThe pirate is still wandering around the town and the crew is waiting for him. Pull him along the right direction by tilting the phone towards the boat!\n\n
Nevertheless, you will see that the fuzziness of his tottering cannot be completely controlled in this way and the movement has a great deal of randomness still.\n\n
Try a couple of times­ until you reach the boat and observe how the walk is modified by your intervention. Score 1000 points and you will move to the
next level.</string>
    <string name="end_level1B"></string>
    <string name="level2C_intro">\n\nHey! The boat is about to leave! Hurry up! Drag directly the pirate step by step: the faster you tap on the screen, the longer the step of the pirate!\n\n

You can also to control the direction by tilting the phone as in the previous level.\n\n

Will you manage to beat the randomness this time?\n\n</string>
    <string name="learn_more_main_menu">
        Pirate’s walk:\n A mathematician would describe the pirate\'s movement as a “random walk” - because all the steps the pirate takes have different lengths and seem to be in arbitrary direction. These processes, which include series of chance moves, are widespread in both daily life and scientific research: follow the link to see some examples: http://goo.gl/6ljFpC .
\n\nParrot\’s feather:\n Scientists have recently thought that randomness in the process of gene expression can be a major source of phenotype variability. It means that every individual in a population of living organisms is unique and differs from anyone else, even its twin or clone, in appearance and behaviour. Follow the link to learn about this phenomenon http://goo.gl/eLEFNc .
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_main_menu">
        The team:\nThe project “Random Walks” is created by Aleksandra Aloric, Silvia Bartolucci and Barbara Bravi, PhD students in the Disordered Systems group, King\'s College Mathematics department.\nThe app is developed by Sari Nusier, a Bachelor student of Computer Science and Management at King\'s College London.\nThe graphics is designed by Anne Odling Smee, Director of Design Science.\n\nFor more information visit our website at http://goo.gl/DFq44C.\n\nAcknowledgements:\nKing\’s College Cultural Institute Early Career Researchers (ECR) scheme and NETADIS (FP7 – Grant 290038).\n\n\n\n\nDisordered Systems:\n http://www.kcl.ac.uk/nms/depts/mathematics/research/disorderedsys/index.aspx\n\nDesign Science:\nhttp://design-science.co.uk\n\nCultural Institute:\nhttp://www.kcl.ac.uk/cultural/culturalinstitute/index.aspx\n\nNETADIS:\nhttps://netadis.wordpress.com\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="level2A_text">        You are about to enter one of the parrot\'s feather cell, where you will explore why each of these animals appear so colourful and diverse!\n\nNow instead following a pirate, follow the movements of big molecules - transcription factors inside the cell. As the transcription factors take part in the process called “gene expression” and play important role enabling the creation of mRNAs - try to create as much as possible of them!\n\nTo read further about DNA, mRNA and transcription factors and how they interact in gene expression networks select “Learn more” in the side menu or visit http://randomwalkspp.wix.com/pirateparrot \n\nTap on the organelles to discover their names!</string>
    <string name="level2B_text">You have just seen how random walks at the cell level contribute to differences in gene expression. Adding up all these microscopic events, through a chain of connected biochemical processes, may give rise macroscopically to variability among parrots, e.g. in colouration patterns.\n\nFrom 1 cell to 2, from 2 to 4 … to millions. Cells grow and replicate by splitting into cell daughters. Sometimes it happens in biology, especially during the development of a newly born organism! You will see that a random partitioning of molecules follows the randomness in their walk</string>
    <string name="level2C_text">Now gene expression in two cells evolves independently! Observe how different mRNAs lead to different colours. Is the number of TFs the same in the two cells? Do they move in the same way? Do they reach the promoter region at the same time? Some randomness can be seen in these slight differences and slight differences emerge also out of this randomness.</string>
    <string name= "level2a_endText">Transcription factors are constantly colliding with organelles and other smaller molecules which constrain their random walk. There is a variable chance for them to reach the promoter region on the DNA and for mRNAs to be created: the number of mRNAs is linked to phenotype changes.\n\nDid you manage to create some mRNAs? Go to level B or, if you are not satisfied, start the process again… Randomness  will help you produce a different number of mRNAs and change colours in the parrot\'s feather!</string>
    <color name="Level1">#F1D495</color>
    <color name="Level1_game_background">#DED9D9</color>
    <color name="level2_game_background">#c2d5f0</color>
    <color name="Level2">#91C8C2</color>
    <color name="BlueLine">#5069a9</color>
    <color name="RedLine">#ef7861</color>
    <color name="GreenLine">#01a05f</color>
    <color name="YellowLine">#864ca3</color>
    <color name="Bk0">#C1D5F0</color>
    <color name="Bk1">#CBD5EF</color>
    <color name="Bk2">#D5D5EF</color>
    <color name="Bk3">#E7D5EF</color>
    <color name="Bk4">#F3D5DF</color>
    <color name="Bk5">#FFD5DF</color>
    <color name="Bk6">#FFD9D6</color>
    <color name="Bk7">#FAD5CF</color>
    <color name="Bk8">#FAD6C8</color>
    <color name="Bk9">#D5D5EF</color>

    <string name="title_activity_level1">Level1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2">Level2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_start">Random Walk</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2_animation">Level2Animation</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2_b">Level2BActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1a_game">Level1aGameActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1b_game">Level 1B</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2a_game">Level2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level2c_game">Level 2C</string>
    <string name="title_activity_level1c_game">Level 1C</string>

</resources>
